<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
  <content contentuid="h3b552af2gff7fg465eg8d57gfea79ad1a2f3" version="1">A backpack containing all the Sample Equipment Mod items.</content> 
  <content contentuid="he13660ffg121ag486cgbaaeg66ffe8445360" version="1">Sample Backpack</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5375081g8f5cg4a8cgb9ccg9acdb4b9a09f" version="1">A dwarven smith, Silverblade, forged this hammer and two other items: a girdle of frost giant strength and a pair of gauntlets of ogre power. His intention was to gift them to his son, who was then a high officer in the dwarven armies, fighting the giant and ogre tribes of the area. Unfortunately, Silverblade's son died just after the completion of the three items and before they could be gifted to him. In grief, Silverblade himself donned the girdle and the gauntlets. Taking up the Hammer of Thunderbolts, he went to battle against the giant folk. He died valiantly.
  
  Alone, the Hammer of Thunderbolts is a powerful magical weapon, but when merged with the gauntlets of ogre power and the girdle of frost giant strength, the hammer is transformed. This transformation requires magical assistance. The Hammer of Thunderbolts is then capable of doing an additional +8 damage as well as instantly killing any giant or ogre that it strikes.</content> 
  <content contentuid="ha3204afeg82a6g4b94gae67g4ec8bafe7a25" version="1">Hammer of Thunderbolts</content>
  <content contentuid="h0cb5800bg243dg4c74ga393g870e1cc2787b" version="1">Many centuries ago, a trumpet archon named Chin Yi fell in love with a mortal man in Shou Lung and swore to protect him from enemies should he ever ride to war. When that time came, however, Chin Yi's patron goddess Kwan Ying forbade her to intervene, not wishing to contribute to the bloodshed. When Chin Yi's beloved was cut down by a yuan-ti warlord, her grief was terrible and her wrath immediate: Ignoring Kwan Ying's warnings, she flew onto the battlefield and took up her beloved's katana, using the blade to cut down the warlord and all those who served him. She continued the slaughter of the yuan-ti army until Kwan Ying herself appeared before her, arms open and eyes full of sympathy. "If it will stop this slaughter, I will ease your pain and end your suffering."
  
  "I do not wish to end my suffering," replied Chin Yi. "I wish for my fury to sound throughout the ages, now and forever." Wanting to help her servant, but not wishing to unleash such powerful fury on the world, Kwan Ying bound Chin Yi's spirit to the blade of the man she had failed to protect and then hid the weapon in a warrior's tomb. The tomb was later infiltrated and the weapon stolen, and although Chin Yi's cries could no longer be heard through the steel of the blade, her vengeance was as brutal as ever.</content> 
  <content contentuid="hdadbec9fgf58bg4b9dg91dag637568f2fa84" version="1">Celestial Fury</content> 
  <content contentuid="h6685a889ge073g4425g9f32g2ab02c65a358" version="1">On a hit, the target is Stunned unless it succeeds a Constitution Saving Throw.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha1917f3dg22eag450bg9ae1gf79044fe00d4" version="1">Booming Thunder</content> 

  <content contentuid="h26f3c5ccg92f6g4c5fgb12fg6a8c471a6338" version="1">The finest bow crafted by Gesen Khan, this weapon draws energy from another plane, firing spears of lightning instead of arrows... and therefore never requiring ammunition of any kind. It is said that Gesen prepared to retire from his craft after selling the invaluable weapon, only to have the bow wrested from his grasp by a thief who used it to end Gesen's own life. A side effect of the bow bestows protection from electricity upon the user.</content> 
  <content contentuid="he8c53b1fgddbeg45e5gad7dg44066ec83a2b" version="1">Shortbow of Gesen</content> 

  <content contentuid="h58c26eacg2c9eg4623g98afg7479837ed9bb" version="1">Carsomyr is a weapon of legend, perhaps one of the most powerful blades ever forged on Faerun, though its origin and history is thought purposefully forgotten so that the sword itself shall never overshadow the importance of the struggles that must be fought today. It is infused with the very essence of virtue and requires as much from any Paladin who would hope to wield it. The evils of the realms must truly stand aside when this weapon is brought to bear, their magic dispelled with a word, steadfastly resisted with ease. Carsomyr also harbors a special distaste for the forces of evil and chaos, and such creatures must fear additional damage from its touch in battle.</content> 
  <content contentuid="hecf38e25ge960g4424g9e4egb728464ad052" version="1">Carsomyr</content> 

  <content contentuid="hcd2357d0g028fg40b5g9f17gddc05fd53024" version="1">Carsomyr deals an extra [1] to evil creatures.</content> 
  <content contentuid="h34ff420ag358dg4f3cg9737g85c7aa3d4807" version="1">Holy Power</content> 

  <content contentuid="hee6f2213g553ag44cbg82baga09abd35be11" version="1">Carsomyr overwhelms nearby foes' spells without rest.</content> 
  <content contentuid="h1dd17a66gede3g4d3fg9a24g2b842d177004" version="1">Relentless Melee Counterspell</content> 

  <content contentuid="hae0b6a4egfee3g4ac0gbc84ge737ec164337" version="1">Carsomyr's dispell extends even to foes far away.</content> 
  <content contentuid="h80f83c13gc838g43acgb97cg9c20cfcca8c4" version="1">Ranged Counterspell</content> 
  
  <content contentuid="h124a0714ge56dg4bd9ga2f2g87174701502d" version="1">Only Paladins that are Pure of Heart may wield Carsomyr. All else will take [1] while holding Carsomyr.</content> 
  <content contentuid="hbb0db8e2gc394g4db9gba59g8a2092914212" version="1">Pure of Heart</content> 

  <content contentuid="h32951c26g4126g4d3fg9310g48505bc83d8b" version="1">Whether created specifically for use in the service of Torm or appropriated at some point in the long history of the church, paladins of the Loyal Fury have made good use of Daystar in their battles against evil undead. Through magic or blessing it is empowered with the Sunray, a force of pure life energy so potent that it slays both living and unliving.</content> 
  <content contentuid="hf55997b2gc3d2g4830ga60dg7ea6ddcde261" version="1">Sunblade +2: Daystar</content> 

  <content contentuid="hf12a6b9fga096g4877g8821gfacb30faf207" version="1">Daystar deals double damage against all forms of undead.</content> 
  <content contentuid="h99a31bf6g0649g4f69gb588gd691c492d988" version="1">Undead Destroyer</content> 

  <content contentuid="hc4d9162dg6b50g4cffg9478g465ad4dea004" version="1">Enemies take [1] damage and must [2] or be Blinded for 2 turns. Undead take [3] and must Save vs. Spell or be destroyed.</content> 
  <content contentuid="hd202b4d5g3f7dg436aga56dg1a2499b50bd1" version="1">Sunray</content>

  <content contentuid="h49df63d2g61dfg4651g8baag9aa857683341" version="1">Daystar counts as +4 to attack and damage against evil creatures.</content> 
  <content contentuid="h1130e6e1g2433g4b6fgb41ag3e65651aeaa8" version="1">Holy Power</content> 
  <!-- <content contentuid="" version="1"></content>  -->
</contentList>